https://psl-equip.com/privacy-notice/

Skip to content
Privacy NoticeJulie Powell2017-04-13T01:46:30-07:00
PRIVACY POLICYPSL Lab Supplies respects your privacy.
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of PSL Lab Supplies.
External Sites
PSL Lab Supplies is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows PSL Lab Supplies to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and PSL Lab Supplies does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to PSL Lab Supplies and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through PSL Lab Supplies have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
Go to Top
